Hello, learn German in Hindi,
welcome to the next episode.
Today we are going to learn important in German
means command cycle or giving orders, what does it
mean when we speak in Hindi, come here, go here,
what is all this ignorance and it is
simple that any command is
given to the person in front, so
in German also it will be the same that
command will be given for the second person form, so what are they,
hmm, tu
means you, here means you all and ji means you, so
you can make imperative in these three forms,
so we will see these three forms now,
first of all ji ji means you have to say halwa power, that
you have tea, so what will be a simple, it's very simple
normal sentence,
ji 3 hours, now in the imperative, any
form of work will always come first in the imperative, so do you
want to give it a little emphasis,
bring the difference first, that wrinkles
son, 3 hours is simple or you have to say it,
say it slowly, you, so what will be the
expression, district exam, Premchand ji
Longtang if you want to make it a little softer then
daughter you can apply it for 3 hours winter so
upon his request is that further means you
almost request someone ahead with permission so that is
why this register but if the actual permission is
not given then it is far above you here here
which is given in you friend you then we
learn that
laughingly he said you simple so what to do in this
listen carefully any class people
put two phones of it make two frames of it
remove tasty from it for example
what will be the storm of twinkle twinkle if you remove tasty from
trend prince what will be the
trick so * apart from tea drink print you have to
say a similar thing learn german learn
german so what will happen with garlic
remove the lens from it lemon so one layer dont now
you both take Priyanka drink or glue
this at that time itself why did
not the elements read like this so I will tell you that also here
we did this because it
benefits us in irregular verbs for
example with a helpline helpline
feel  Why was he left
because the album has been removed, Hill Mishti
removed,
that film Help Me Hills Near or if you want to say it, then
what will happen, there will be a touch of trouble,
it has been removed, Taurus ascendant, Taurus ascendant
is simple, ride, just a small thing because
after a long time they ask that
many people in my class had asked me, look at
this example, look at the example of liaison lisam, the
distance list is the distance leaves and its chord is all, so
what happens to this thing, please, now
we have not even one of the ST, so it takes
some time, but look carefully,
when you made the distance list of your writing, did you
give it a stress, or did you
say to take it, I will give you 31, is it
correct, then if you take it back, then
how will you give that rate, that is because
garlic has leaves, that we
gave it while doing two, clarity ahead, if
you are finding it a little hard right now, then live or
religion and simple steps with a, this is difficult
for all the work ideas, editor and updates
time, Sanjay, spot for simple content
Fixer, everyone understood the sunshine, right now in the third or
fourth year, I mean you are talking to a lot of people
whom you don't have to respect,
you too - in such a situation, I do
n't know much about where this situation comes up, this situation is
in my mind that brother you are teaching teachers and children, there a simple
situation appeared, I understand, so
basically you and the children have to
talk, children, speak calmly, then what will happen,
you are simple, make this raw,
date sheet, this kind of a
special form, this
press tinder spirit long correct, here
children should drink milk, calendar print chilli,
tinder trick chilli, absolutely SIM player, nothing,
now this thing is important to keep in mind
that when you were
making Quikr, then you will use ji, that is,
chemical on Zee TV, you do not need to speak in the other two forms,
deposit and not
really, modern, are you used to it or not,
hence, love is considered on contract, print or
print chilli,
it is clear only when ji's attitude is  So the
concept of the given text is clear, it is very simple
that it is in the beginning and the balance and depending upon the distance, it is
far away, this is its restriction, very
simple concept,
we complete one more small thing that is to join the time, just
like I told you that to be always
works in any way, this point world
works differently here also, so how does it work, that
simple, I will give you, if you tell me, be
polite, then how will it happen,
see because pathetic place, if he says
you are flying, on this wave request,
still he says you are flying, then what will happen,
come please right-click and if children have
control, then the side will be next, there are some more
small options,
they will always be there and will be there
in every language,
what is most important for us, see,
understand the basic rule, we have seen three basic rules, first of all for the
half imperative,
what did we do for the distance, that is, do not
put the palm outside and that is
pregnancy for the worst position, after that
we saw the distance form  What to do for the grooms,
make a distance for it, remove the mode, set the
print, here you do not have to say distance,
printhead and after that we also learned that
if you want to use it many times then
share it similar to that also, friend, there is
no need to say it, Tinder print chilli, Tinder
print chilli is very simple but there is nothing
hard in it, I hope that you
all have understood the cancer, we will meet
in the next episode, thank you